<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<atom:link href="http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<title>
			MOON Case Project Diary | beverlymoon.com
		</title>
		<description>MOON Case Project Diary</description>
		<link>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2011 21:59:27 PST</pubDate>
		<lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2011 21:59:27 PST</lastBuildDate>

					<item>
				<title>Launched | MOON Case Project Diary</title>
				<link>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/launched</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2011 10:00:00 PST</pubDate>
				<guid>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/launched</guid>

		<description>
by Beverly Moon
					<img alt="Launched" src="http://beverlymoon.com/media/img/diary/launched.jpg" />
					<p>We were in San Francisco this weekend, visiting friends and celebrating November birthdays. Thought it would be a good time to push that big green &#8220;launch&#8221; button amongst close&#160;friends. </p>
<p>It&#8217;s <a href="http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/mooncases/moon-contact-lens-case">officially up</a>! Thank you Teo Dabov for being my first&#160;backer.</p>
				</description>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>Lights, Camera, Action! | MOON Case Project Diary</title>
				<link>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/video</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 23:00:00 PST</pubDate>
				<guid>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/video</guid>

		<description>
by Beverly Moon
					<img alt="Lights, Camera, Action!" src="http://beverlymoon.com/media/img/diary/video.jpg" />
					<p>We worked all weekend to shoot the Kickstarter video. I&#8217;m very camera shy, so it wasn&#8217;t easy. I think we got some good product shots and it&#8217;s going to be a simple and direct video. Thank you Ben for the peanut M&amp;Ms, Cineskates, and all those funny conversations caught on video. I also could not have done this without my husband who was the camera man and sound engineer behind all this. Love you&#160;guys!</p>
				</description>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>Kickstarter | MOON Case Project Diary</title>
				<link>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/kickstarter</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2011 10:00:00 PST</pubDate>
				<guid>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/kickstarter</guid>

		<description>
by Beverly Moon
					<img alt="Kickstarter" src="http://beverlymoon.com/media/img/diary/kickstarter.jpg" />
					<p>Happy Halloween! Got a treat in the mail today from <a href="/projects/contact-case/kickstarter">Kickstarter</a>. My project has been accepted. Just need to make the video and we&#8217;re&#160;off!</p>
<p>You guys should check out the other great projects that <a href="http://kickstarter.com">Kickstarter</a> is hosting. It&#8217;s a great site that offers crowd source funding to creative&#160;individuals.</p>
				</description>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>Website + Kickstarter | MOON Case Project Diary</title>
				<link>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/website</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2011 10:00:00 PST</pubDate>
				<guid>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/website</guid>

		<description>
by Beverly Moon
					<img alt="Website + Kickstarter" src="http://beverlymoon.com/media/img/diary/website.jpg" />
					<p>Just made the final tweaks on the website and it&#8217;s officially live! Joe has been working so hard these past few weeks and did an excellent job. Thanks for those of you that gave feedback. We are very nervous and excited. We will submit our form to <a href="/projects/contact-case/kickstarter">Kickstarter</a>&#160;tonight!</p>
				</description>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>O-ring | MOON Case Project Diary</title>
				<link>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/o-ring</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2011 10:00:00 PST</pubDate>
				<guid>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/o-ring</guid>

		<description>
by Beverly Moon
					<img alt="O-ring" src="http://beverlymoon.com/media/img/diary/o-ring.jpg" />
					<p>Experimenting with o-rings. I found out that there are many casual contact lens wearers. So ideally, the cases would be close to airtight to prevent evaporation over longer&#160;periods.</p>
				</description>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>Eco Felt | MOON Case Project Diary</title>
				<link>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/felt</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2011 11:00:00 PST</pubDate>
				<guid>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/felt</guid>

		<description>
by Beverly Moon
					<img alt="Eco Felt" src="http://beverlymoon.com/media/img/diary/felt.jpg" />
					<p>I am cutting the eco felt that was delivered yesterday and am very happy with it so far.  Always keeping the environment in mind, it&#8217;s 100% tan wool with no post processing applied and aligns with the low environmental impact philosophy that I have been trying to adhere to with this project.<br />
</p>
				</description>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>Photoshoot | MOON Case Project Diary</title>
				<link>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/photoshoot</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 10:00:00 PST</pubDate>
				<guid>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/photoshoot</guid>

		<description>
by Beverly Moon
					<img alt="Photoshoot" src="http://beverlymoon.com/media/img/diary/photoshoot.jpg" />
					<p>I wanted to take nicer shots of the products for the website, so today Joe and I went to my office to set up a more &#8220;professional&#8221; photo shoot. It was great to experiment with lighting and a fancy camera. It&#8217;s pretty amazing to really enjoy learning something and work toward a goal with my husband. It&#8217;s not like work at all. We were pretty happy with the results. Thank you Schaar for helping us set&#160;up!</p>
				</description>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>Friends | MOON Case Project Diary</title>
				<link>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/friends</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2011 11:00:00 PST</pubDate>
				<guid>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/friends</guid>

		<description>
by Beverly Moon
					<img alt="Friends" src="http://beverlymoon.com/media/img/diary/friends.jpg" />
					<p>When you have any kind of personal project that requires extra energy that you really don&#8217;t have after your 9-5 job, it&#8217;s a blessing to have great friends that support you and encourage your work.  Thanks to the Munsons who have been such a support from the very beginning.  Ben even pulled out his dremel to help refine the design. Also, Edward for your engineering mind and tips, the Cinco product team who shared my enthusiasm and those who gave me that extra pat on the back to keep this going. You know who you&#160;are. </p>
				</description>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>Packaging | MOON Case Project Diary</title>
				<link>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/packaging</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2011 11:00:00 PST</pubDate>
				<guid>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/packaging</guid>

		<description>
by Beverly Moon
					<img alt="Packaging" src="http://beverlymoon.com/media/img/diary/packaging.jpg" />
					<p>Exploring packaging for the product. I&#8217;m not a graphic designer by any means so I&#8217;m not going to attempt to do any fancy illustrations. Just a simple and straightforward design that allows the product to be the hero. I will be sourcing local packaging and choosing materials that are eco-friendly. I didn&#8217;t do my research very well for my samples so the first boxes were not made in the <span class="caps">USA</span>. Future products will ship only in made in <span class="caps">USA</span>&#160;packaging. </p>
				</description>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>First Samples | MOON Case Project Diary</title>
				<link>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/first-samples</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2011 10:00:00 PST</pubDate>
				<guid>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/first-samples</guid>

		<description>
by Beverly Moon
					<img alt="First Samples" src="http://beverlymoon.com/media/img/diary/first-samples.jpg" />
					<p>First 45 samples were ready to be picked up. Talked to Stuart, an <span class="caps">SPM</span> employee who&#8217;s been more than helpful along this process, about the troubles that they&#8217;ve been having with the lid and how the taper is causing the material to kick up and&#160;crack. </p>
<p>I thought that this whole process was almost over but it seems like there might be more revisions than I anticipated.  Good thing is that I have a few to give away and feel out how users are liking&#160;it. </p>
				</description>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>Joe | MOON Case Project Diary</title>
				<link>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/joe</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 10:00:00 PST</pubDate>
				<guid>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/joe</guid>

		<description>
by Beverly Moon
					<img alt="Joe" src="http://beverlymoon.com/media/img/diary/joe.jpg" />
					<p>This is our first project collaboration together and it has been pretty gratifying. Joe has been glued in front of the computer for the past few weeks creating a website for the&#160;product. </p>
<p>He is being so open creatively and never says &#8216;no&#8217; to an idea even though it&#8217;s his first website. Full Moon in effect.&#160;;p</p>
				</description>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>Second Sheet | MOON Case Project Diary</title>
				<link>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/second-sheet</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2011 10:00:00 PST</pubDate>
				<guid>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/second-sheet</guid>

		<description>
by Beverly Moon
					<img alt="Second Sheet" src="http://beverlymoon.com/media/img/diary/second-sheet.jpg" />
					<p>I just dropped off another sheet of Corian&#174; at <span class="caps">SMP</span> to finish up the first sample run. I had a hard time trying to find Corian&#174; sheets for the first run of sample&#160;production. </p>
<p>Lots of headaches talking to various local shops and big box retailers. I finally got in touch with a rep and he graciously opened his own home to let me rummage through his piles of samples. So excited to see so many colors and&#160;options. </p>
				</description>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>First Article Review | MOON Case Project Diary</title>
				<link>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/review</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2011 10:00:00 PST</pubDate>
				<guid>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/review</guid>

		<description>
by Beverly Moon
					<img alt="First Article Review" src="http://beverlymoon.com/media/img/diary/review.jpg" />
					<p>I found a few details that need to be corrected before the first sample run.  This is the final 10% of the design process that makes a product special, giving attention to little details that most users&#160;appreciate.</p>
				</description>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>First Article | MOON Case Project Diary</title>
				<link>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/first-article</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2011 10:00:00 PST</pubDate>
				<guid>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/first-article</guid>

		<description>
by Beverly Moon
					<img alt="First Article" src="http://beverlymoon.com/media/img/diary/first-article.jpg" />
					<p>Just picked up the first article to approve today! It was so satisfying to finally see a physical sample after months of designing and researching. 
It was nearly perfect. There are just a few changes that I&#8217;ll have to make but I&#8217;m really happy with the design and result. It&#8217;s been wonderful working with&#160;<span class="caps">SPM</span>.</p>
				</description>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>Small Parts | MOON Case Project Diary</title>
				<link>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/spm</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2011 10:00:00 PST</pubDate>
				<guid>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/spm</guid>

		<description>
by Beverly Moon
					<img alt="Small Parts" src="http://beverlymoon.com/media/img/diary/spm.jpg" />
					<p>Just dropped the materials off at <span class="caps">SPM</span>. Should have a first article to approve by next week. I&#8217;m so nervous and excited at the same&#160;time.</p>
				</description>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>Colors | MOON Case Project Diary</title>
				<link>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/colors</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 10:00:00 PST</pubDate>
				<guid>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/colors</guid>

		<description>
by Beverly Moon
					<img alt="Colors" src="http://beverlymoon.com/media/img/diary/colors.jpg" />
					<p>Picking out colors for the first sample production was not that easy since there were so many choices and I was limited to only 2 or 3 colors. Joe and I took some samples to our bathroom and looked at neutral colors that might work well in most&#160;homes. </p>
<p>I decided that &#8220;Natural Grey&#8221; and &#8220;Glacier Ice&#8221; were the two colors that could really look beautiful on a bathroom sink. Super excited and nervous about the color&#160;choices!</p>
				</description>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>Corian&#174; Samples | MOON Case Project Diary</title>
				<link>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/corian</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 10:00:00 PST</pubDate>
				<guid>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/corian</guid>

		<description>
by Beverly Moon
					<img alt="Corian&#174; Samples" src="http://beverlymoon.com/media/img/diary/corian.jpg" />
					<p>I had a hard time trying to find some Corian&#174; sheets for the first run of sample production.  Lots of headaches talking to various local shops and big box&#160;retailers. </p>
<p>I finally got in touch with a rep and he graciously opened his own home to let me rummage through his piles of samples. So excited to see so many colors and options. I&#8217;ve been looking at the material online for the past few months and to actually feel the samples and see the colors was really&#160;helpful.</p>
				</description>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>Final Design | MOON Case Project Diary</title>
				<link>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/final</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 11:00:00 PST</pubDate>
				<guid>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/final</guid>

		<description>
by Beverly Moon
					<img alt="Final Design" src="http://beverlymoon.com/media/img/diary/final.jpg" />
					<p>Just finished the final design and sent the files to <span class="caps">SPM</span> for them to review. Just waiting for the Corian&#174;&#160;sheets.</p>
				</description>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>Concepts | MOON Case Project Diary</title>
				<link>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/concepts</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 10:00:00 PST</pubDate>
				<guid>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/concepts</guid>

		<description>
by Beverly Moon
					<img alt="Concepts" src="http://beverlymoon.com/media/img/diary/concepts.jpg" />
					<p>These were the two final concepts that I ended up with back in March. I looked at a &#8216;pill&#8217;-shaped design that was similar to other plastic designs in the market and a rounded square design that was more distinct and sculptural. After much discussion and thought, I decided to go with with the rounded rectangle one because it was more disruptive and different than the other designs out&#160;there.</p>
				</description>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>Beginning | MOON Case Project Diary</title>
				<link>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/beginning</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2011 10:00:00 PST</pubDate>
				<guid>http://beverlymoon.com/projects/contact-case/diary/beginning</guid>

		<description>
by Beverly Moon
					<img alt="Beginning" src="http://beverlymoon.com/media/img/diary/beginning.jpg" />
					<p>It&#8217;s been almost a year since the idea first popped into my head and more than a month since I actually took the initiative to get started on this project. Today, I brought Joe along to the place where the cases will be&#160;manufactured. </p>
<p>There were some numbers and a few technical details we needed to hash out before we could get this rolling. I was excited when Stuart, my point of contact at Small Parts, took me on the tour the last time I visited, so I was glad when he offered to show Joe around. It&#8217;s nice to see the machines, the workers, and the space behind everything and I wanted to share that experience with him. The sound of drilling mixed with the smell of oil and the mass of the machines&#8230; all of it is just so raw and physical. And it&#8217;s surprisingly calm in&#160;there. </p>
<p>I ordered the materials to make 50 sets tonight and they should arrive next week. So if all goes well&#8230; we might start the first production by the end of next week.&#160;Wow.</p>
				</description>
			</item>
			</channel>
</rss>